{
    "subject": "resource/Duane_Carter",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/description",
    "object": "American racing driver",
    "human_readable": "Duane Carter is an American racing driver.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7603092789649963,
            "question": "What type of racing does Duane Carter participate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.736263632774353,
            "question": "Is Duane Carter known for any specific achievements in racing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6837350130081177,
            "question": "What teams has Duane Carter raced for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6290008425712585,
            "question": "What motivates Duane Carter to race?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.601003110408783,
            "question": "Where is Duane Carter from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5897589325904846,
            "question": "What nationality is Duane Carter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5896434783935547,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges that Duane Carter faces in his racing career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5340153574943542,
            "question": "Does Duane Carter have any plans for future racing endeavors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5215319395065308,
            "question": "Are there any notable rivals that Duane Carter has competed against?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49615079164505005,
            "question": "Has Duane Carter won any major races or championships?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Duane Carter is an American racing driver.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2488_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable rivals that Duane Carter has competed against?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2488_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Duane Carter have any plans for future racing endeavors?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2488_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the challenges that Duane Carter faces in his racing career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2488_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2488_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2488_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2488_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2488_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2488_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2488_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2488_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2488_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2488_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2488_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that Duane Carter was an American race car driver, which confirms this statement."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide several pieces of information that support the statement \"Duane Carter is an American racing driver.\" The details include his participation in various races such as the Indianapolis 500, midget car racing, and IndyCars, which are all related to racing. Additionally, there is explicit mention of him being born in Fresno, California, further supporting his status as an American racing driver."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}